

Profile

Self-taught and passionate Software Developer with 5+ years in the 8200 Intelligence Unit. I bring a versatile skill set, from Full Stack Development all the way to Windows Drivers Development. Looking for a fresh challenge where I can make a real impact on the world.

Employment History

Software Developer, 8200 Intelligence Unit

2021 - 2023

- Design and Development of low-level security applications for Windows in C and C++, both Kernel-Mode and User-Mode.
- Low-Level Windows OS research.
- Leading development projects as a technology expert.

Full Stack Developer, 8200 Intelligence Unit

2018 - 2021

Managment, Design, and Development of a large scale automation system:

- Micro-services of Python and Node.js, based on Linux Docker containers.
- Frontend based on React.
- Databases of MSSQL and MongoDB.

Pilots Course, Israeli Air Force

JANUARY 2018 - APRIL 2018

Education

B.Sc. in Computer Science, Open University

2021 - PRESENT

OJT of Apollo Course, 8200 Intelligence Unit

202

Acquired skills in Research and Development of Cyber Security applications.

OJT of Hermon Course, 8200 Intelligence Unit

2018

Acquired skills in Cyber Security and Full Stack development.

Shoham High School

2014 - 2017

Graduated with highest honors with GPA of 96.

Majored in Computer Science and Physics.

Details

Tel Aviv Israel +972 50-477-3722 guybasri@gmail.com

Links

linkedin.com/in/guy-basri

Skills

Python

C++

Windows Internals

Software Architecture

Cyber Security